Hi! This is AyachoMadoham and Mikinin of Chain Salutuals of the Mikinin World.
Today, I think it was a chatting video before.
We were talking about the catchphrases of the members, and Nanase's catchphrase was "I'm a big fan".
Nanase-chan's catchphrase is as difficult as a big joke.
We were talking about how we'd like to introduce other members' catchphrases if there are any interesting or good ones.
So today, I looked at all the catchphrases of all the members and picked up one that I would like to introduce.
I've picked up a few that I'd like to introduce here.
I'd like to introduce them here.
First of all
Saho Iwatate!
She's a member of Team A called Saho.
This one is quite famous.
There is a template or something like that.
First, Saho...
Let's start the vocal exercises, ladies and gentlemen.
Yoo-hoo!
But the fans just say
Yoo-hoo back
And then Saho will say Saho, and then the fans will say Saho again, and then the fans will say Yoo-hoo times, and then Saho will say Saho again, and then the fans will say Yoo-hoo again.
And then the fan yells back "sahoo," and then the fan yells "sahoo," and then the fan yells "sahoo," and then the fan yells "sahoo," and then the fan yells "sahoo," and then the fan yells "sahoo," and then the template is added to.
And then the fans would say "yoo-hoo" and then Saho would say "it's too early".
I think it's great.
If it's not a bad word, it's not a bad word at all.
And again, Saho says it's too late, but isn't that too long? I've been thinking that.
I think it's too slow for too fast, but Saho is long.
I think of Saho as a character, a bullied salesman, a cute character.
So this is the catch phrase that shows the best of Saho.
This is the first one.
Next is Hinako Okuhara from Team K. We have been good friends on Team B, but Hinako's catchphrase is, "The gods have given me life for 19 years.
I'm from Shimane Prefecture, and I cherish the relationships I've built with you all.
I've been thinking that a girl who's always joking around is not a character that's been given life by the gods, and it's been a while since I've heard of her.
He's a representative of Shimane Prefecture, which he says is called the land of the gods.
He says he's trying to include his hometown, but it's really in character.
And the way he says it, he doesn't express a single ounce of emotion. Yes, the gods gave him life, and he's been dead for 19 years.
I've always loved this... personally, I'm on Team A and Team B.
I'm a member of Team A and a member of Team Mochi, which means I'm a representative of the prefecture I'm on Team B, and Misaki Kawahara is on Team B.
Misser's catchphrase is "Saga is the best!" I'm Misaki Kawahara, aka Mr. Kawahara from Saga Prefecture, famous for the Yoshinogari Ruins.
This is another surprise, and the first one is that she is forced to say that Saga Prefecture is the best in the world with her own catchphrase.
Another member of this forced series is Kyoka Yamada, who is now the voice of the same team, but she's also a member of "You too, starting today" and she's a reinforcement girl, and then everyone has to be a reinforcement girl, and then everyone has to be a reinforcement girl, and then everyone has to be a reinforcement girl.
I like the forced series a lot, but you guys, the s station of the magnet is Sakaguchi, and the n station of the magnet is Nagisa.
I'm not trying to make a bad thing out of it, but I really respect it.
I'm not saying it's a bad thing, but I really respect it.
What about the songs we don't have?
They said we shouldn't clap our hands together! To be honest...
It's so shrieky when he claps instead of me!
Well, it only works when the band members say it, but it was so shoe-horned in.
It was also very funny!
And Miyupon Omori!
I was with her at the first stage.
I love her looks so much!
Super idol!
The face of an idol who looks like she could be in Halo Pro.
I thought she was really cute.
At her first stage
Her catchphrase was
Deco-pon-supon, mew-pon with all your might
She said...
Do you want to put your pom-poms in? Something like that.
I guess he really wanted to use that mewpon.
That's why he was looking for something with a "Pom-Pom" on it.
I'm willing to give up on the "dekopon" for a hundred steps.
Suppon? Something like that.
Like a turtle? I'm like...
That's amazing. That's amazing.
She was a teenager back then, right?
She was so cute.
Doing this kind of stuff? I don't know.
Like, "Dekopon," "I can't see a thing" kind of stuff.
It was shocking.
Last one.
Karen Yoshida
I looked at the list of catchphrases for all the members.
I was a little curious to see the catchphrases.
I went to YouTube and looked up Karen Yoshida's catchphrase.
I found the one she used at the event.
I found the best one, the one that everyone responds to when you ask them to do something like this.
Fans were like, "Flip, flip, flip! And then they were like, "Oh, yeah, turn it over, turn it over.
And then they would flip it over and flip it over and flip it over and flip it over and flip it over and flip it over and flip it over. And then they say, "Here's the calendar!
Wait a minute. Flip, flip, flip the calendar! It wasn't a catchphrase anymore. I was shocked, really.
It's still a little bit related to "Saga Prefecture is the best" and so on. And they're really stirring things up.
They're very aggressive, really. They'll get really excited on the spot, and when they get excited, they'll stretch it out, right? I saw it three times.
But when I asked Naru-chan about it, and when I asked someone from the same team, she said, "No, I'm not like that when I'm the main actor in the so-called "nativity" event.
I want to see it until I'm really serious.
I've never been able to say it with you, so I'm going to stop now.
I've never been able to say it with you.
They're getting excited!
I'm going for it! Let's do it!
Calendar!
Awwwwwww!
It's really fun!
Flip, flip, flip!Flip, flip, flip, flip...
Flip, flip, flip, flip!
Oh my God, it's on point!
Calendars!
Calendars don't do that in commercials.
Seriously, it's funny.
It's great!
I'd love to hear Karen Yoshida's catchphrase live sometime!
So, that's it, I've introduced AKB members' catchphrases.
What do you think?
They are really funny!
But I couldn't put them all here.
There are many more!
So, if you know any of the members...
I like this catchphrase, and I've had a lot in my past, but I'm not going to get into that now, so I'd love to hear your guesses.
I'm trying to keep it under wraps, so if you have a favorite catchphrase for a member, please let me know in the comments section.
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get in touch with me.
you